<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<prefix name="frmguidedtour" label="frmguidedtour" language_tag="en" language_label="english">
        <key name="guide_title">
            <value>
            guided tour
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> buttons >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="button_activateGuideline">
            <value>
                Guided tour
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="button_next">
            <value>
                Next
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="button_prev">
            <value>
                Previous
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="button_nextPage">
            <value>
                Next page guide
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="button_previousPage">
            <value>
                Previous page guide
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="button_skip">
            <value>
                Ignore guide
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="end_guided_tour">
            <value>
                End guide
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> page unavailable >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="page_unavailable">
            <value>
                No guided tour is available for this page.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> mobile >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="mobile_info">
            <value>
                Welcome to {$site_name} guided tour. You can see next and previous guided and close this guide temporarily. You can also dismiss this guide.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="mobile_notifications">
            <value>
                This option can show you a list of notifications.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> mobile groups >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="mobile_groups_info">
            <value>
                In my groups page, there is a list of groups in which you have joined. Choosing any of them would lead you to that group page.
            </value>
        </key>


        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> mobile friends >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="mobile_friends_info">
            <value>
                In friends page there is a list of your friends. You can be redirected to any of their profile page by choosing their name. You an also search among users by find new friend button.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> mobile dashboard >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="mobile_dashboard_info">
            <value>
                In dashboard page all activities that are related to you are displayed.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> mobile mailbox >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="mobile_mailbox_info">
            <value>
                In mailbox page, all your messages are listed. By choosing any of them you will be redirected to that conversation's page.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> mobile setting >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="mobile_setting_info">
            <value>
                In setting section, you can access profile, edit profile and your preferences. You can start guided tour again by choosing "guided tour".
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> index >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="index_info">
            <value>
                Welcome to {$site_name} guided tour. You can see next and previous guided and close this guide temporarily. You can also dismiss this guide.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_guideLink">
            <value>
                Guided tour will be shown in any page by clicking on this option.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_profileLink">
            <value>
                Profile options, preferences and other parts related to your accounts are accessible here.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_notificationLink">
            <value>
                All notifications are listed here.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_messages">
            <value>
                New messages will be shown here.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_groups_widget">
            <value>
                In this section last and most favorite groups are represented.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_users_widget">
            <value>
                In this section you can see newly joined, online and top users

            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="index_pics_widget">
            <value>
                In this section, last and best images are shown.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> dashboard >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="dashboard_info">
            <value>
                In dashboard page, all activities related to you are shown,
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="dashboard_news">
            <value>
                In dashboard news section, you can share contents like file, video, image and questionnaire and you can set privacy level for them.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="news_create">
            <value>
                Using this button you can create new blog content.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> groups >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="groups_info">
            <value>
                Groups page contains groups' information and activities.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="groups_myGroups">
            <value>
                All groups in which you are joined are shown here. You can also search among them.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="groups_latest">
            <value>
                This section contains public groups.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="groups_invitations">
            <value>
                All invitations sent to you are accessible from this section. You can accept or reject them.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> profile >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="profile_info">
            <value>
                Profile page contains all information about you.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="profile_details">
            <value>
                In this section you can see your information. Yoo can also change each item privacy level from here.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="profile_news">
            <value>
                You can see news about yourself here. You can write new content here or add a new questionnaire.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="profile_picture">
            <value>
                Profile picture is shown here. You can change it by clicking on it,
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="profile_aboutMe">
            <value>
                You can add some information about yourself here. This information will be visible for all users.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="profile_contacts">
            <value>
                You can see your all friends here.
            </value>
        </key>
    <key name="profile_groups">
        <value>
            You can see all your groups.
        </value>
    </key>
    <key name="profile_toolbar_buttons">
        <value>
            You can update your profile information and change your password by using these buttons.
        </value>
    </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> competition >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="competitions_info">
            <value>
                In competitions' page, all competition held at {$site_name} are represented.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> events >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="events_info">
            <value>
                This part contains events' information and activities.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="events_myEvents">
            <value>
                This part shows all events which you have engaged in. You can also search among them.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="events_latest">
            <value>
                This section contains latest general events.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="events_invitations">
            <value>
                In this part, you can see all events invitations sent to you. You can accept or reject them.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> blogs >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="blogs_info">
            <value>
                In blogs page, all created blogs are represented. You can also search among them and create new blogs.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="blogs_latest">
            <value>
                This section is a list of users latest posts.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="blogs_create">
            <value>
                Using this button, you can create new blog content.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="blogs_top_rated">
            <value>
                In this section you can see a list of top-rated blogs.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="blogs_most_discussed">
            <value>
                In this section you can see a list of most-discussed blogs.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="blogs_browse_by_tag">
            <value>
                In this section you can see a list of blogs according to the tags.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> photo >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="photo_info">
            <value>
                In images page, you can see and manage images. This page contains latest uploaded images and uploading new images.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="photo_create">
            <value>
                Using these options, you can upload new image or create an album of a group of images.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> video >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="video_info">
            <value>
                In videos page you can watch latest uploaded videos and search among them. You can also upload new videos.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="video_create">
            <value>
                By using this button you can add upload new videos.
            </value>
        </key>
    <key name="video_toolbar_guide">
        <value>
            using these options, you can see a list of videos according to latest uploaded, top-rated, labels, your friends' videos and your own videos.
        </value>
    </key>
        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> news >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="news_info">
            <value>
                News page contains latest news. This page allows you to search content, create new content and search labels.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="news_tools">
            <value>
                In this section you can access most discussed and top rated topics, and latest contents and create new content.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> hashtag >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="hashtag_info">
            <value>
                Hashtag page contains used hashtags in website's contents. The size of hashtag represents its use rate. You can also search among hashtags.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> questions >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="questions_info">
            <value>
                Questions page contains all created questionnaires. You can participate in questionnaires or create one.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> frmterms >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="frmterms_info">
            <value>
                Terms page contains detailed conditions of using website and terms. To be informed of terms and conditions, please read this page.
            </value>
        </key>

        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> frmcontact >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="frmcontact_info">
            <value>
                In contact page, you can send mail to website's managers.
            </value>
        </key>
        <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> active-sessions >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
        <key name="active-sessions-info">
            <value>
                Active sessions page contains different information about user activities such as their last activity time, the browser they use and other related information.
            </value>
        </key>
        <key name="active-sessions-login">
            <value>
                This page provides details about user's login such as the time they logged in, browser they used or their IP address.
            </value>
        </key>

        <key name="active-sessions-active">
            <value>
                This page provides information about user's active sessions such as their last activity time, their browser and their IP address. You can also terminate all other sessions in this page.
            </value>
        </key>

        <key name="active-sessions-terminate">
            <value>
                In this part you are able to terminate all sessions except for the current one.
            </value>
        </key>

        <key>
            <value>
                With this button you are able to terminate the session you which can't be the current one.
            </value>
        </key>

    <key name="page_has_no_guide">
        <value>
            Page has no guide
        </value>
    </key>
    <!-->>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>> frmquestions >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
    <key name="frmquestions-info">
        <value>
            On the polls page, you can view polls created by users in other sections, such as the recent section.
        </value>
    </key>

    <key name="all-polls">
        <value>
            In this section you can see all the polls.
        </value>
    </key>

    <key name="popular-polls">
        <value>
            Only popular polls are displayed in this section.
        </value>
    </key>

    <key name="friends_polls">
        <value>
            Only polls created by your friends are visible in this section.
        </value>
    </key>

    <key name="my_polls">
        <value>
            In this section, the polls that you have created can be seen.
        </value>
    </key>
</prefix>

